So, I'm having a blast
The swallow is not going anywhere without Heungbu.
not me
you caught me
You came running to me
So save me
Do your best to protect me
It's a person
Ha, right
This crazy green temple
That's right for me...
I don't have time to be like this.
Hurry up and tell me
I need to tell you this news
Ugh!
Is the Crown Prince alive?
It's annoying
Jericha
Where is Do Seung-ji now?
- child
- Mmm, it's delicious.
Hello
- Oh, now there's something to eat.
- Wow
- Now come here.
- Really, why are you doing that?
Uh, uh, hmmm
Well, what are you doing now?
I know who you are...
each other
Because I have nothing to be proud of
Please send that court lady away.
No, how...
You
He killed the crown prince, ha.
Would you believe it if you were me?
You'll have to believe it.
My father will offer it for me
Because you are looking for a sacrifice.
no
Why am I still...
Jeundaegun 5 village outhouse
Prince Jeun instead of crown prince
Didn't you try to promote him?
What do you want?
Let Prince Jeun sit on the throne.
And next to it
I will sit down.
What should I do?
The girl on the left
Jeundaegun
You were trying to make him a crown prince?
yes
The crown prince is still alive
They tell me to clean up after them.
mama
What should I do?
Now I understand
Then it makes sense
- yes?
- The woman on the left is holding out her hand.
Take only half
Prince Jeundae
I feel like dying at the hands of someone else
Hahahahahaha
Hahahahahahaha
Oh, it's heavy, oh, oh, oh
When I saw it, it was definitely, huh?
I'm going to treat you like this
That's why you saved my leg
Otherwise
I can't explain it, huh?
Ha, oh, Mr.
Now again
Tsk tsk tsk tsk
We're there, we're there, we're there, alright
Ooh, ooh, ooh
Wow
Oh no
This guy now, Mr.
Aren't you sleeping?
Oh, oh, oh
Ah, ah...
ha
Ugh...
Ah...
I'm sorry
Like a fool
Why are you grabbing that hot thing?
foolishly
Ah!
Ah...
Hey, aren't you sleeping?
wake up, hey
Mr. I
not a swallow
Isn’t this Nolbu’s wife?
Oh, it hurts.
Ah...
Did you sleep well?
Hey, hey, hmmm
Well, are you feeling okay?
I guess I'll have to stop by the doctor's office.
Are you feeling very unwell?
Please take a look
I said I would do it, ah...
Ha, thank you
yes
Now, please take a look at that kid's hands.
yes, i understand
Jiyu?
Oh, no, it's okay
It's okay
My palms are all clenched like that.
Oh, it's okay
If you don't get treatment, I won't get it either.
- Look
- Yes?
Let me release this again, okay?
Ah, oh, oh, oh
That's enough, that's enough
- Oh, take it off, quickly.
- Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
- W, w, here, yes.
- Oh, yes.
So stubborn
It would have happened a long time ago
Hurry up and open your eyes
Grand Prince Sari
Hanyang Sangsangcha’s servant has arrived
‘Tea servant’?
You are
You sent a letter?
Ha, you're alive, brother.
Definitely to Officer Yoon
I delivered it, but after that day
I can't meet Naekwan Yoon.
The government has no intention of moving.
Even entering my palace
has been limited
Someone saw you coming back
You're disturbing me
Okay, I'll go myself.
To Your Majesty first
Shouldn’t we let you know?
Anyone in the palace
This is not a situation I can trust.
go quietly
I will bring you with me.
Mistress!
madam!
Okay, I'm in big trouble.
Lord Jeundae, Nari...
Why Daegun?
In the great army saga
Your letter has come out.
What is the reason behind hiding the letter?
I want to ask
Why is there a book that I have never seen before?
Did it come out of my house?
If you do this, you will
The fact that you are alive
Are you saying you didn't know?
I knew it, so
I'm going to save you
I sent someone
The reason I sent someone
Was it to save Hae Hae?
Did you try to harm me?
How can we sort it out?
large joint
what am i doing
Are you trying to harm His Highness!
The great army
He is the eldest son of His Majesty the late King.
If Queen Jangjeong
If only I hadn't been falsely accused
So, to the king
They told me never to hand over Bowie to him.
If it had not been for the support of His Majesty the late King,
It should be the great commander
You must have climbed the dragon podium.
Thinking like that
I've never tried it.
The Great Queen Mother also
Would you think so?
Absolutely not!
Grand Prince Nariga
If you tried to assassinate me
I have served you all my life.
Would you have sent a member of the Left Committee?
go quietly
I will bring you with me.
Ah, are you okay?
Wait a minute
Do you come to your senses?
Ah...
I will go
If the commander moves
Everyone in the palace will know
the author
The situation is unfavorable to the commander.
I'm making it
What did I do?
Ikwisa, who protects the crown prince
When you can't serve Utjeon properly
That you will be severely punished
Don't you know?
Sometimes you even have to risk death
But
Such a high treason criminal
I guess the commander has let me run away now.
If it's because of Jeundaegun
go back
Nothing will change
I lost
But do you know what?
The sewers are always
I chose suicide.
Jeundaegun, if even a single hair gets hurt,
I will run to Uigeumbu
The bridge you run to
Do you want to leave me alone?
If you break it
I will go even if I have to crawl
So you want to stop me
Break my neck first.
Do you think I can’t do it?
Is there anyone outside?
yes
Did you find it?
Lock Woohee in the room
Until the national wedding takes place
Don't let me take a single step
Father
I'm sorry, lady.
Just touch my body
I'll bite my tongue and die
What is it again this time?
It's mom
Let's see
That's right
Nari, please come down.
Who are you?
Who sent them?
I wish I got the money
Shouldn’t we take care of loyalty?
How is it, Nari?
Get down
Huh?
It's dangerous to be on a horse
Get down and look straight ahead.
never look back
Ah
yes
sleep...
Shall we cry now, Nari?
Nari
Oh, what?
The boy is cowardly
I will live alone
Looks like he's taking a step back
- That's very funny.
- Mr. Lee
Come here
Guys like you
It's not worth buying
I mean, huh?
Please give me that axe.
An ax that I trust even when I swing it
The guy who got his foot stamped
Why don't you swing it better?
I saved your life for no reason
I saved your life for no reason, Mr.!
From Sun Tzu's Art of War
'With the ability
He said, ‘Make it look like it’s not there.’
Well, it's covered.
It's not an ability that can be hidden.
My tactic is this.
What are you saying again?
head on
- Ha!
- huh?
Uh, uh...
Ah...
- Ah...
-Are you okay?
yes
It's here!
Wow
Ujjandaeyu?
um
It will get my attention
run away
I hope you survive this time
please
Nari!
- I'm also a bitchy woman, huh?
- Oh my!
- Ah
- What, what, what
Mr. Lee
Ouch!
Ah
Ugh
Ouch!
Ah, ah!
Oh my!
uh
- Oh my!
- Oh, evil.
Oh my mom, my mom
Oh, my goodness
Hey, Pasha
Hey, wow!
Ugh!
uh?
Ugh, ah...
Ugh, evil
Hey
Mom, uh, uh!
Ugh
- Ugh!
- no!
Oh my
Uh, Nari, ayu.
Mom, mom, oh
Please save me, oh
Hey!
Hey! Ugh
Shin Won-ah
Nari
I was wrong, it wasn't...
Ah! Ah, ah...
You were alive.
was alive
thank you
Please stay alive
Thank you, Shinwon, ha.
degradation
Rather, Prince Jeun is more dangerous.
Why Prince Jeun?
Is the Crown Prince alive?
Prince Jeun’s work
After the Crown Prince returned...
You can come back
Are you sure?
They tried to assassinate me
Those who are pushed to the edge of a cliff
What are you afraid of?
Really, Prince Jeun.
They said they tried to assassinate the crown prince.
Do you think?
The truth is
doesn't matter
What's important is
That you are alive
So you're safe
You have to come back.
Your Majesty loves
who sacrificed to protect everyone
That's me
Do as you wish.
I will obey your command, Your Majesty.
The fact that the left upper body moved
I plan to keep Prince Jeun alive.
There is no
But the problem is
Someone who wants Jaune dead
It's not just a left injury.
What do you mean by that?
It worked out better
Sejado
authentic
There is no Jeundaegun either.
In a situation like now where there is no successor,
If Joo Sang dies...
The next succession designation is
It is with the great queen mother.
Jaune goes into exile
Left upper nerve
When I went to Jaune
I will poison Abamama.
Mama, not even for a moment
The Gyesannyeon incident
Because you've never forgotten
There are eyes of the world
The image on the left is none other than Prince Jeun.
I won't be able to send you into exile.
before i go
I will deal with Jaune.
From Yeongdeok to Hanyang
within six or seven days
When did you send the letter?
Today is the fifth day
Ha, it will soon be six days.
From now on, at full speed
It takes two days to run.
It's too much for my body right now.
Besides...
From Yeongdeok to Hanyang
on all land routes
My men are in ambush.
you guys will never
You won't be able to enter Hanyang.
- Ah...
- I still can't come to my senses.
Hey, the overland roads are soggy.
Is the waterway clogged, huh?
What, the boatway collapsed? Tsk
What do you mean?
How to get there by boat
Is it there?
Please follow me
A stunning swallow nearby
I got it right
Oh boy, I am this again
I'm the type of person who can't live with debt.
Oh no, again...
When will this happen again...
That backpacker
The life of the Segok Line manager
There is something I saved you.
As a repayment
I'll show you three curves.
Tomorrow morning
We will arrive at Mapo Ferry.
My moon is to that child
I owe you a very big debt.
Are you going to Hanyang together?
I saved the national copy several times.
I have to give thanks.
The case is Boryeong.
Can’t you do it separately?
Boy
If it wasn't for that kid
Would you like to draw these three curves?
And what about cases, huh?
Do you know that this can only be done with money?
Shinwon, why are you like that, huh?
Are you affectionate? Tsk
Hmm
Thank you
Please do as you wish.
Did you laugh at me, did you laugh at me?
-You got hit less, right? very just
- Ah
no, that's not it
This isn't me laughing.
Because the night air is so cold
I coughed
This is what I did
I think you misunderstood
Just stay still
Uh...
this clothes
Looks good, huh?
huh?
If you stare at the river like that
Well, does it mean the ship is going fast?
Come sit down
I'll just change this bandage.
Oh no
After
Prince Jeun was arrested for treason.
Is it you, Grand Prince? No...
Wait a minute, the reverse is...
Isn’t your life in danger?
i have to go
Because only I can save Jaune
But
I'm scared, I'm afraid I'll be late
You know that saying?
-The more urgent...
- Go back?
Why are you in such a hurry to go back?
The more urgent you are, the more thorough your strategy is, right?
As soon as you arrive at Maponaru
this bandage
Just tie it up
Eat well and go straight, okay?
yes
Go straight and come back
Stay at the top of Hanyang
Don't fly to Gangnam
Why is it Gangnam all of a sudden?
You said you were a swallow
The swallow that won’t leave Heungbu behind
Ah
wait and see
You will be the one to ride it
A very formidable guy
Don't be very surprised when you receive it.
Don’t worry, right?
Yeyu, a woman with material desires
Ah
ha
Ha, the moon is so pretty
Ah
That's right
It's not even a full moon, but it's pretty
Me, Nari
I will follow too
Nari...
Oh, who are you looking for?
Nope
Get out of the way
Before I slit my throat and die
What are you doing!
If you do my lady
Don’t you know that you are the one who does it?
Hey
It definitely wasn't clothes like that.
Stay at the top of Hanyang
Ying
Wow
Take care of yourself
Yeah, I got it.
let's stop
Earlier, on that street
Did you see Prince Jeun going into exile?
What island in Yeongdeok are you going to?
I saw it
Hehe, let's sell it too
You have to go to the palace before passing the exam.
'Squint'?
Your Majesty, please skip the breakfast table.
Morning Surah at the Four Hours
After a meal, take herbal medicine.
Go to the palace right away.
But Jeundae-gun is also dangerous.
If the place of exile is an island, the image on the left is
On Jaune's boat
will get the job done
Because it would be the neatest way.
If you want to drag them all the way to the Walpaedeul
You can't divide your workforce
Damn, you have to choose
Did you prepare well?
yes
The ship that Prince Jeun rode on was
It will be broken by the storm
It worked out better
Sejado
authentic
There is no Jeundaegun either.
In a situation like now where there is no successor,
If Joo Sang dies
Your Highness!
Your Majesty, the Crown Prince
They say you're back
Stop by right away
Abama's poisoning
Anyone can stop it
The exile of Prince Jeun
It cannot be stopped without His Majesty’s mission.
Only I can do this
This is the official sent along with the letter.
that I am alive
It will be a gift
you go to the palace
I'm going to Jaune
Brother
Brother!
charge
Soja, it's too late.
Disturbing my mind
Confused public sentiment
The son's sin of disloyalty and disloyalty
please ask
no
It's done because you gave me life
That's it.
Also, the road to come is difficult
Although I have passed the risk of death many times,
With the help of Prince Jeun
I was able to enter the palace safely.
To Prince Jeun
Please give me a big reward.
You should do it that way
It's no coincidence
The crown prince senses my desperation
I guess I guessed it right.
It seemed like I didn't see it
Circumstances inside the palace
I had it all figured out.
Immediately after Prince Jeun went into exile.
I will also poison the chief minister.
The time when Joo-sang takes the herbal medicine
I guess I remembered it all.
The crown prince
It's a crime
As soon as the Left Committee came in
In this decoction bowl
That there is arsenic in it
They noticed it right away.
I guess that's what you told me
yes
I guess today is
At the Great King’s Vision
It must be the day of the Heavenly Rain Creed
What are you going to do now?
To combat left injury
The help of the Great King Vision
absolutely necessary
Yes, Your Highness...
Tried to poison you
If we pass this time
Is there no next time?
Use it for yourself in the future
When left and right fell
Before the Great King
To avoid losing power
You need a weapon too
I'm sorry, brother.
Why you?
It's Do Seung-ji's fault.
It's not your fault
Brother, do you trust me?
I'm really depressed
Couldn't they have tried to assassinate him?
Uh, trust me
Because you are my family too
And I know the real culprit
I saw the guy who shot me on the cliff
What...
It's the girl on the left.
If it wasn't for the moon
I would already be dead
What do you mean ‘moon’?
Did you meet Dal-i at Sinjusa Temple?
uh?
Oh, how do you know that?
Dal-i went to Sinjusa Temple?
Ah, I heard
I'll stop by before I leave
Ah
Oh, that's the moon
Well, for a moment I
I told you to stay in Hanyang.
They say it’s because they have nowhere else to go.
Well, stay at your house for a moment
Is it okay to stay?
Is Dal-i in Hanyang now?
Uh, it's at the top of Hanyang.
What if I send Dal-i there?
In the eyes of Hanyang’s upper management
What are you going to do if you stand out?
Why is that?
Ah, brother
Halma Mama is in the East Palace.
Court ladies pushing in steadily
Through Hanyang Sangdang Acting Director
These are the women who came in.
The moon and the poor mother
I heard they look alike, that's it
The fact that you saved my life
If you know
Would you like to leave Dal-i alone?
Hey
Hey, hey, hey
Quick, quick, quick, go fast, huh?
Hurry, go quickly
The moon brings me quickly, quickly
Huh? quickly, quickly
Run! Run, hurry, run!
I heard you almost went into exile.
Hey, are you okay?
As you can see
I'm glad
Well, are you feeling alright?
- Oh, it's okay...
- You suffered a gunshot wound.
Oh, the road ahead is also difficult.
Because I wanted to fight
There are a lot of wounds
You shed a lot of blood
Proper treatment
I don't know if you received it
- Uh...
- Yes, what is the meal metaphor?
Did you eat properly?
Oh, my energy has diminished a lot.
You should eat well
If you want to gain strength,
You have to eat everything well, no matter what.
Just by looking at his face, he seems like a picky eater.
So why hasn't there been an answer since a while ago?
Questions are pouring in without a break.
Didn't I have time to respond?
Did I do that?
Oh no
- Um...
- And then with my brother.
It looks like we've gotten a lot closer.
I worry about myself and my brother.
The concentration is so different
I'm sad
Oh my, why are we getting closer?
Well, it's because of the money you get, eh.
Eosa Nari paid compensation very well.
I heard you did a lot for me.
If I receive that money, I can repay my debt.
Well, it won't be like that.
If that's what you're worried about, don't worry.
They're all yours
Everything...
What happens to me now?
The Crown Prince is back
Nothing will change
The crown prince dies again
Even if the head of state dies
Nothing will change again
You are in the place I decided
I will sit down
As you said, I
There is no alternative but you
However, the clean and jerk is different.
When the chief priest dies
Another royal friend
Just put him on the throne and that's it
But
Why is it that Prince Jeundae
Are you saying it can't be done?
Because he is the son of a late king
Because he is the son of Queen Jangjeong.
If you're worried about revenge
It's raining
Prince Jeun forgives my sins
Instead, I even tried to hug him.
And the biggest reason now is
It's you
Prince Jeun to me
I won't take revenge
What is the basis?
Isn’t it your love?
You are for Prince Jeun
kill the crown prince
Prince Jeun is for you
gave up one's life
Like this, love is
makes humans weak
You are swayed by Prince Jeun
There's no guarantee it won't hit me
So now it's a pipe dream
Wake up
Oh, you sent all of this back?
why?
no
To Hanyang
Except the money it cost to get there
They say they sent it all back.
no, what
There's all that business, huh?
I think business is right.
I took only Eunja here.
Sam is very accurate.
What to do with all of this stuff?
Ah... then
With as small and expensive items as possible
Get ready, okay?
Well, so it doesn't seem burdensome, huh?
Yes, after
After
Wait a minute
Yes?
Sir, the teacher
If you wear these clothes
You said you would like it
ha
Just something like this
Did you try to buy a meme?
Ah
I knew you would be like this
Just one set of clothes
I never dreamed I would be so moved
How can it be so beautiful?
A thousand things like me
If you wear clothes like this
I will be amazed
If you don't wear those clothes, they'll make you angry.
you don't know but you
You did such a great job.
If you find out later
I made it with just one set of clothes
So much so that I hit the ground and regret it
Come out wearing it.
Let me see if it suits you well.
Why again?
Somehow I'm glad to see you
Even from the sound of my footsteps, they knew it was me.
To talk like that
I feel like so many things are broken
To put it back in place
you
Why do you always climb up high places?
Oh my mom
Because you will be in heaven
Mom...
Do you want to see it?
Is that your dream?
my dream
To the old days
going back
No way
Because of those words
Did you plan this?
Even for a moment, I dream of being a great general.
I have never forgotten
So
It became my dream
It's a dream because it can't come true
You too now
wake up from that dream
Umm
I'm not sure if this is right
Oh, I also do things like this...
Ah...
guest
I guess you were there
Kid...
Not a guest
She's my woman
The woman with whom I will have a family
So, would you please go back now?
As you can see
I have a prior contract
I haven't torn up the contract yet.
stop
I think I'm mistaken
Even if you give me orders
There is no one who can do it
Just a noble woman
It's time to give orders to the king.
Because there hasn’t been any until now
The reason I followed your words
It was only love and now
The one who loved you
dead
Ah
I'm sorry
Are you okay?
Uh, okay
You came first, right?
Eosa Narirang
Than Jwasangdaek’s wife
You came first, right?
Now the order is
Is it really that important?
Why don't you catch me?
To save
Me or that woman
In order for everyone to live
That's the only way
Hani
can you please help me
I still have your contract.
yes
What power does a guy who owes money have?
Follow me
My goodness, you look happy.
Ha, indeed
Boy, he looks happy, hmm
Well, any gentleman
Returning favors and being kind
It's such a joy, huh?
Well, something like that, hmm.
I hope you have the heart of a gentleman.
soon
You will have a national wedding.
The women around me
That too, from a poor mother.
If you see a woman who looks just like you
That backpacker
Not only is it dangerous, but
Monitoring of contusions for degradation is also
It will get worse
Just a repayment for a lifesaver
That's it.
So it's the last time
Today is
today is the last day
Oh my, it's so pretty...
um
Nari!
Again, again, again
Smile so pretty again
Hey, this is it
Wow!
How come
Even more than the gold and silver treasures I sent you
I think this soup has a lot of flavor.
Where is this soup
It's just soup, huh?
Save my leg too
Gukbap Indie who saved Nari’s heart
yes
indeed
It's old soup.
Now, I ate soup and rice too.
Goodbye forever and ever with Nari.
Already?
I heard there will be a falling flower show later.
Well, why don’t you go see that?
'Falling Flower Play' Yu?
Yeah, a while ago
Got missing but returned safely
For the sake of lowering the tax base
I heard there is a falling game going on.
um
That's it
I’ve seen all the eight falling flower games.
Even if I saw it
Still
Hanyang falling flower play
It'll be the first time
Yes
Let’s watch together, play with falling flowers.
Hey! This is it, right?
Write it
Write...
Just a moment
Wow, I'm angry, oops
I have a habit of not wearing them.
you are over there
wait a moment
Where are you going?
It'll just take a moment
Well, me and Shinwon
Because the two of us will go and come back
Sedol you are
Stay here, okay?
Nari...
What, suddenly?
Suitable for fall leaf type
Where are the flower shoes, um
Report it once anyway
I don’t think I’ll wear them.
Just buy roughly.
As it is the last flower scene
You have to choose carefully
With pretty flower shoes, huh?
Why are you so unloving baby?
Hmm
Wow, I'm so crazy, I'm dying.
Why are you like that, like a dog stuck in poop?
Ah!
in front of me
About poop and puppies
Don't join us!
- Uh...
- Wow, that’s okay.
I'm surprised, Mr.
Huh? Oh my
What are the pairs?
Oh, oh...
Oh, oh
ho
Hmm
Wait, wait, wait
Wow, that woman...
You look familiar
Ah, the original beauty
Isn't it obvious at a glance?
Wow, it's really pretty... huh?
Isn’t that the backpack seller?
‘Back seller’?
Yes, my master.
no, that
Jipyeong adult’s family
I'm a bitch who got caught up in holladang.
I'm sure
Yeah?
Hmm...
It's been a while
That one...
Our Lady Ipandaeam
Let's see.
Yes you bitch!
On the subject of menial wealth compensation
Only a nobleman can wear it
Are you wearing red silk clothes?
Even though you disturb the laws of the river
Do you want to be safe?
I apologize.
If you give me just a moment
Change your clothes quickly and come back.
Because I changed my clothes
Do you think this is something that can be solved, huh?
Cut off my bitch's head right now
The crime of disturbing the laws of the river
You can ask sternly
I committed a mortal sin
If you forgive me just once
Uh, I'll do anything, anything.
Wow
Please just save me, oh
That's right, that's right
I have to do everything
Ah, this is the truth
Degradation, degradation, degradation!
deterioration, degradation
child, that child
Why did you come here to protect me?
What, why, why, why, why?
Why, speak, speak
Oh my, my, my, my...
Wow
I feel sorry for that subcompensation, so let’s go
Well, I happened to get caught by Yifan.
Hey, why are you like that?
Are you wearing red silk that doesn’t match your status?
Wealth compensation, red silk
Isn’t that the backpacker from earlier?
Since when have you been following me?
Ever since before?
Now that you've been caught, go back.
I have somewhere to go
Lee Pan-eun
He is my father's closest confidant.
No longer in my father’s eyes
Don't turn to dust
Let go
A truly lowly backpacker and
Are you trying to start a family?
There's nothing I can't do
I wanted to start a family with you too
It's me
Huh?
Now, follow me.
no
No, no, why here?
Well, go home, okay?
Oh, this is crazy...
This precious gentleman’s clothes
I took it all off
Now pick up my sins that have fallen to the ground
Are you hungry even if you eat it?
The person who is the equivalent of a judge
How can I follow the common law?
Threaten the woman
Are you trying to harass me?
A person like a captain indeed
sit high in the court
Is it right to discuss politics?
This is crazy
These four years are truly life
Looks like it was worth it, huh?
Get your bitch now, huh?
How dare you
How dare you do that
Oh, Nari, Nari, you're in big trouble.
Put away the knife
Oh, this, oh...
Three, three years lower
'Lower'...?
Hey, get out of my way
Get out of the way, out of the way, out of the way, out of the way
What did I say
I'm not sure what to do...
How long on earth
Are you going to run wild like a thunderbolt?
No, that's me...
Why don't you know how to wait?
When in danger or when injured
When you fall, you have to stop and wait
I should have screamed for help
until I solve it
I should have waited!
I am Nari, ayu...
Deterioration
Why wait?
do my job
Why are you solving this problem?
Because it’s not just your job!
This is now
Do you think it's just your job?
That face resembles my wife.
clearly stated
So definitely
I wish I wore that outfit
Is that what you said?
Using the example as an excuse
me lady
No
Instead of a poverty-stricken mama
Are you playing with dolls?
what?
you said so
Are you going to keep doing this carelessly?
Why are you angry?
Isn't that it?
I am so lowly
I dare to resemble the face of a poor mother.
Because I suffered such humiliation with that face
Isn't it?
yes
you are right
If you understand, with that face
don't jump into danger
Don't be humiliated, don't come forward!
That you're not my wife
I know it well
I'm not confused anymore
I won't be shaken
So take this
Don't be in my sight again
What are you doing now?!
It's mine now, isn't it?
Hani
I will do whatever I want.
stop
It's a person
What are you doing now?
How dare you accept the gift of a crown prince?
Throwing it to the ground
This is treason and disloyalty.
This high treason criminal
Are you going to leave it as is, sir?
Put down this sword
If Prince Jeun steps forward,
Things get bigger
please
please stop
This blood
It's because of the great army
Ah...
degradation
I feel unfair.
All of this is a self-made play by Mr.
They sent a girl to break me down.
This is what Jwasang planned.
The woman on the left
yes
What did the woman say?
When Prince Jeun becomes the Crown Prince
Make yourself the Crown Princess
I asked you to make it
Baby
They say he assassinated me
To me
You can never come back
That story
Who did you do it to?
I've never talked about it in this much detail.
If you do that, shut your mouth.
Jeundaegundo and the female tableau on the left
Don't say anything more
If you want to live
Ah...
Oh no
Nari
The wound on the neck
It doesn't seem that deep
The hurt in my heart
It seems deep
It's okay
I'm broken by greed
bigger than the weight
I'm going to carry salt poison on my back
The bag breaks
Doesn't it break and leave it behind?
Just one set of silk clothes and a pair of flower shoes
Is there a burden you can't carry?
Who broke it?
No you
Somehow it doesn't suit me
I said I was happy
Something like this just
It wasn't right for me.
Flower shoes? pestilence
As far as my feet go
Phew, then
Is this okay?
Hey, can I wear these?
I bought it quickly on my way home.
It's Mituri
Flower shoes for you
It's not because they don't fit in.
How can it be only to Do Seung-ji?
Did you scare me like that?
Don’t you know the real culprit?
'Cause I found out why
Let’s call it a day and disperse for today.
They are all disloyal people
I'll just go now too
It looks like my wife is hurt.
Whether it's the tip of your tongue or your fingertips
A blade at the end of all
There are only those holding it
Sometimes
what kind of touch
What kind of eyes
Because it is the most sincere and true answer.
Me too
It is a desire for revenge that started with love.
I just want to get my revenge
If you trample on Prince Jeun’s love,
In that child's heart
It just leaves one more scar
Haona
It's better than looking for luggage.
The woman on the left
He assassinated the emperor
Finding a deposit is
Wouldn't it be faster?
Revenge is never too late
Rather than going faster
It's more important to take the right path
ha
Isn’t that a bit weird?
low, for now
calm your mind
Returning to the palace...
A
How can that heart
Will it sink that quickly?
- 'That heart'?
- You must feel uncomfortable.
in a place with a lot of people
That's what happened to you
That's not how you feel.
no, that's right
Sedol Nigga
It's been a while since I said the right thing
Oh, really?
I am very angry now
bring that child forward
We'll never meet again
Probably not, hani
A way to resolve this resentment
It will never be, if not now
So I'm going
To relieve this resentment
Ah, let's go
I gave first aid
I need to go get treatment
Change into these clothes.
What is it?
Are you there yet?
The clothes you are wearing now
That bright blue is the opposite of you.
Because you are a fall leaf type
Anyway, this color suits me better
Change your clothes quickly and come
I don't go because of the clothes.
Are you following me?
Following me
I saw it while passing by
I stopped when I saw it
When I stopped, I realized
my heart
Yes
Thank you
Where can I hear it?
Now
Now tell me
What on earth is that mem?
resentful
The crown prince who is wearing something is making a fuss.
Yes
Why are you so angry?
I use you as a substitute for poverty
I have never played with dolls or anything like that.
Because of a heart I don't even have
Being misunderstood as shameless
very angry
That's not it!
In times like this
I'm saying I'm sorry
I'm saying I did it wrong.
ha
Crown Prince, should you apologize to me?
Make a mistake and ask for forgiveness?
To a single backpacker?
If you made a mistake, apologize
It's the right thing to do
More than a bowed head
It's more embarrassing to have an upright head
How do you not know?
A royal family that does not love its people
There are no people to love
So be afraid of the people.
love them first
not reign
Rule me in accordance with reason.
I don't think you have anything more to say.
I'll just go now
I raised the keynote
in three months
I will become the Crown Princess
What are you doing now...
what are you
What on earth are you?
Why did I take this step because it was the last time?
Are you leaving it here?
Why again in my heart
It takes root!
Ah, ah...
- Ah!
- Ah, ah...
Ah, ah...
Huh?
uh?
If you think about it, swallows
Don't just return the favor
Good luck to Heungbu
Nolbu was punished
It's just a trick with a certain meaning
That damn swallow
I must have mistaken something.
no
A good person like me
There's no way it's Nolbu
I, this precious prince,
- It's missing. Where did it go?
- This lowly backpacker and
The body changes
It's heavenly punishment!
These days, I'm low
Isn’t it really strange?
It's called Lee Gangdol.
Deterioration
What happened!
Like that day
Why not give it a try?
A kiss... a kiss?
The seated figure resembles a poor mother.
If you even look at that face...
What happens when you look at it?
I'll kill you